Guide to the Stuart Elliott papers, 1875-2014 and undated RL.11108
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings File, 1969-2014 and undated; 7
  - 2012, 7
    - 4/25--TV: Curvy Girls, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - 4/25--TV: Vevo, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - 4/26--Cone Edelman, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - 4/26--Oxygen upfront, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - 4/27--Kraft/30 Rock, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - 4/27--New Fronts, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - 4/30--OAAA (Outdoor Advertising Association of America), 2012 (Box 137, Folder 14)
    - 4/30--Under Armour, 2012 (Box 137, Folder 15)
    - 5/3--Bank of America, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - 5/3--Coppertone, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - 5/3--PopChips, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - 5/3--YouTube, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - 5/4--Orbitz, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - 5/7--Mike's Hard Lemonade, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - 5/7--Visa/Olympics, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - 5/7--Visit Denver, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - 5/9--Clear (brand), 2012 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - 5/9--Ritz CrackerFuls, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - 5/10--Mother's Day, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - 5/11--TBS/DumbDumb, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - 5/14--IMAX, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - 5/14--New York Lottery, 2012 (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - 5/14--TV Upfronts, 2012; 2 folders (Box 139, Folder 1-2)
    - 5/15--TV Upfronts, 2012 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - 5/16--TV Upfronts, 2012 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - 5/17--TV Upfronts, 2012 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - 5/18--General Motors/Facebook, 2012 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - 5/18--TV Upfronts, 2012 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - 5/20--TV Upfronts, 2012; 2 folders (Box 139, Folder 8-9)
    - 5/21--TV Upfronts, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - 5/21--With Art Philadelphia, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - 5/22--2012-2013 TV season (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - 5/23--Muse/The Pitch (series), 2012 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - 5/24--Doodle.ly, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - 5/25--Auto Hop, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - 5/29--20 Questions, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - 5/29--Direct Energy, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - 5/29--Mini USA, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - 5/31--Teen Vogue back to school, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - 6/1--Australia, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - 6/1--Bulwark FR, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - 6/1--Pizza Hut, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - 6/4--NY Fire Department, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - 6/4--Pod1 (New York), 2012 (Box 140, Folder 15)
    - 6/4--TV Upfronts, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 16)
    - 6/4--United Talent Agency, 2012 (Box 140, Folder 17)
    - 6/5--JetBlue Game Show, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - 6/5--Made in New York, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - 6/6--Justin Bieber scent, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - 6/7--CW upfront, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - 6/7--Southern Comfort, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - 6/8--American Legacy Foundation, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - 6/11--Cape Cod potato chips, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - 6/11--CNN/CIMM, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - 6/12--Bob Garfield/Barbara Lippert, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - 6/12--CBS upfront, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - 6/12--GoDaddy/Deutsch, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - 6/12--Summer road trip, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - 6/13--ABC upfront, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - 6/13--NBC upfront, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - 6/13--Powerade, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - 6/14--Fox upfront, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - 6/15--Chobani Kids, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 17)
    - 6/18--Advertising High School, 2012 (Box 141, Folder 18)
    - 6/18--Elle Accessories, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - 6/27--Apple Pie Dive, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - 7/2--Bon Apetit/Banana Republic, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - 7/2--Sailor Jerry Rum, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - 7/3--General Motors/Facebook, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - 7/3--Richard Kirshenbaum, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - 7/5--Coke Zero, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - 7/5--Major League Baseball, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - 7/5--Nick Symonds, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - 7/9--E! Online, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - 7/9--Lung Cancer Alliance, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - 7/10--HP/Omnicom, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - 7/10--Staples back to school, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - 7/12--Publicis/Kaplan Thaler, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - 7/13--Perry Ellis, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - 7/16--Blue Man Group, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - 7/16--Fiat, 2012 (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - 7/16--GoDaddy, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - 7/16--Skyy Vodka television ads, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - 7/17--R/GA, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - 7/18--Cadillac, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - 7/18--Fiber One, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - 7/18--Fruit of the Loom, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - 7/20--Commercial Emmy, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - 7/21--Dark Knight ads, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - 7/23--989 onDemand, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - 7/23--Olympics sponsorship, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - 7/23--Run 10 Feed 10, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - 7/24--NBC comedy, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - 7/25--Foursquare "Promoted Update", 2012 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - 7/25--Levi Strauss, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - 7/27--Matt Zucker, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - 7/27--"Simple" brands, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - 7/27--"Simple" brands, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - 7/30--Super Why, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - 8/1--Conde Nast Traveler 25th anniversary, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - 8/22--Macy's Musical, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - 8/24--Crate Barrel, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - 8/27--Advertising Age, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - 8/27--AMC/Dish Network, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - 8/27--Bermuda, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - 8/29--JetBlue, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - 8/29--New Era/NFL, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - 8/29--PopChips/Katy Perry, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - 8/29--Rex Briggs/Marketing Evolution, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - 8/30--Associated Press, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - 8/30--Museum of Modern Art, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - 8/30--Subway, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - 8/31--Bon Apetit Feast or Fashion, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 16)
    - 8/31--Firestone, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 17)
    - 9/4--Gander Mountain, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 18)
    - 9/5--Bud Light/NFL, 2012 (Box 144, Folder 19)
    - 9/5--Senokot-S, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - 9/7--Kirshenbaum Bond Senecal, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - 9/7--Van Wagner Communications, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - 9/7--Visa/NFL, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - 9/10--Glamour Magazine, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - 9/10--Oscar Mayer bacon, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - 9/10--The Standard, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - 9/11--Frank PR/Grace Blue, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - 9/11--People Magazine, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - 9/12--@invisibleobama, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - 9/13--New York Life, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - 9/17--Synogogue, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - 9/17--Woman's Day 75th anniversary, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - 9/18--Benetton, 2012 (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - 9/19--Mendelsohn Affluent Survey, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - 9/20--Publicis/LB:, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - 9/20--Sequence, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - 9/20--Warby Parker, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - 9/21--Get Out the Vote, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - 9/21--Heineken/Discovery/GenH, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - 9/23--Fab.com, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - 9/24--Fresh Direct, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - 9/24--Havas/Euro RSCG, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - 9/24--Marriott Art on the Road, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - 9/25--NASA/TCM, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - 9/25--Oreo Daily Twist, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - 9/28--Advertising Week, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - 10/1--Advertising Week, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - 10/1--Travelocity, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - 10/2--InterBrand, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - 10/3--Advertising Week, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - 10/4--Advertising Week, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - 10/4--CEO Summit Panel, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - 10/5--Advertising Week, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - 10/8--Advertising Week, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - 10/8--Kretschmer Wheat Germ, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - 10/10--Truvia, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - 10/11--ANA Conference, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - 10/15--ANA Conference, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - 10/16--Ted Turner, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - 10/18--Lance Armstrong, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - 10/19--Newsweek, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - 10/19--Political advertising, 2012 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - 10/22--Asics/New York City Marathon, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - 10/22--New York Writes Itself, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - 10/23--Adobe, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - 10/23--Brand Keys Loyalty 100, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - 10/23--Country Brand Index, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - 10/23--Olympics, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - 10/25--Alan Siegel, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - 10/25--Coca-Cola/EkoCycle, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - 10/26--BB Hollywood, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - 10/29--Food Fanatics, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - 10/29--Kia/Blake Griffin, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - 10/29--Mad Magazine, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - 10/30--Toys R Us, 2012 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - 11/1--Hurricane Sandy, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - 11/5--Houston Astros, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - 11/5--State Highway 130 (Texas), 2012 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - 11/6--Macy's Christmas, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - 11/8--Veterans, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - 11/12--Babar, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - 11/12--Coca-Cola, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - 11/12--Ikea Digital, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - 11/13--Nick Brien/InterPublic, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - 11/13--TCM Classic Film Festival, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - 11/14--TiVo/Tim Tebow, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - 11/15--Audit Bureau of Circulation/Alliance of Audited Media, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - 11/18--Jaguar, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - 11/19--Black Friday, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - 11/19--The Contributor, 2012 (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - 11/20--KesselsKramer in Los Angeles, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - 11/21--Brightline, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - 11/21--Christmas, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - 11/25--Human rights campaign, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - 11/26--20 Questions, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - 11/26--Lion King, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - 11/26--Rally St. Louis, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - 11/28--Atlantic City, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - 11/29--AFLAC Christmas, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - 11/29--Peeps/Christmas, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - 11/30--Hindsight Career Project, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - 11/30--TBS/Subaru/DumbDumb, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - 12/3--AAAA, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - 12/4--CBS, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - 12/4--Publicis, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - 12/4--SodaStream, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - 12/5--Peeps E-card, 2012 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - 12/6--Campaigns for E-cigarettes, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - 12/6--eBay Motors ads, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - 12/6--E-cigarettes, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - 12/6--Sid Lee/Belvedere, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - 12/7--Coke/HSN, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - 12/10--Amazing Race (series), 2012 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - 12/10--Samaritans, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - 12/12--Gold Toe, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - 12/12--Nielsen, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - 12/13--YouTube, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - 12/14--Sean Avery, 2012; 2 folders (Box 151, Folder 11-12)
    - 12/17--EHE Window/Light of Life Foundation, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - 12/17--Kantar/Ad spending, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Super Bowl, 2012 (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Super Bowl, 2012; 2 folders (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Super Bowl--Acura, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Super Bowl--Anheuser-Busch, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Super Bowl--Audi, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Super Bowl--Best Buy, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Super Bowl--Blog, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Super Bowl--Bridgestone, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Super Bowl--CareerBuilder, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Super Bowl--Cars.com, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Super Bowl--Century 21, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Super Bowl--Chevrolet, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Super Bowl--Chrysler, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Super Bowl--Coca-Cola, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Super Bowl--Disney, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Super Bowl--Doritos, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Super Bowl--E*Trade, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Super Bowl--Experts, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - Super Bowl--General Electric, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - Super Bowl--GoDaddy.com, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 19)
    - Super Bowl--H, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 20)
    - Super Bowl--History, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 21)
    - Super Bowl--Hulu, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 22)
    - Super Bowl--Hyundai, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 23)
    - Super Bowl--Kia, 2012 (Box 152, Folder 24)
    - Super Bowl--Lexus, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Super Bowl--M, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Super Bowl--Met Life, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Super Bowl--Paramount, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Super Bowl--Pepsi Max, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Super Bowl--Samsung Galaxy, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Super Bowl--Skechers, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Super Bowl--Tax Act, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Super Bowl--Teleflora, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Super Bowl--Toyota, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Super Bowl--VW, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Super Bowl--YouTube, 2012 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Upfronts, 2012-2013; 2 folders (Box 153, Folder 13-14)
  - 2013, 8
    - 1/4--Ace Metrix, 2013 (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - 1/7--Custom Publishing, 2013 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - 1/7--Goodby Silverstein, 2013 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - 1/9--Match/Marketing Drive, 2013 (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - 1/9--Super Bowl/CBS, 2013 (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - 1/10--Lipton Tea, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - 1/11--Anheuser-Busch Super Bowl, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - 1/11--National Milk Moustache Super Bowl, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - 1/14--San Antonio Tourism, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - 1/15--Best and Worst, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - 1/15--Coca-Cola/Obesity, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - 1/16--USA Today, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - 1/17--Expletives in advertising, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - 1/18--Super Bowl, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - 1/22--Booking.com, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - 1/22--Gant Rugger, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - 1/23--Coca-Cola/Hyundai Super Bowl, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - 1/24--Keds/Taylor Swift, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - 1/25--Super Bowl, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - 1/28--3M Post-It, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - 1/28--Barbasol, 2013 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - 1/31--Super Bowl, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - 2/4--National Kidney Foundation, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - 2/4--Super Bowl review, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - 2/5--Super Bowl, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - 2/5--Super Bowl effectiveness, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - 2/7--Barbie, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - 2/8--AARP/Grammy's, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - 2/11--Schiff Nutrition, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - 2/13--Poland Springs/Marco Rubio, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - 2/13--Steve Sachs/OneSpot, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - 2/14--Panera, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - 2/19--Ford Fiesta, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - 2/19--NASCAR, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - 2/19--Snickers, 2013 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - 2/21--Academy Awards, 2013 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - 2/21--Dunder Mifflin, 2013 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - 2/21--NBCUniversal, 2013 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - 2/23--Domtar, 2013 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - 2/25--Delish (magazine), 2013 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - 2/25--McKayla Maroney/Dr. Pepper Ten, 2013 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - 2/26--Academy Awards, 2013 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - 2/27--Bounce TV, 2013 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - 2/27--Edelman, 2013 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - 3/1--Chrysler/Broadway, 2013 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - 3/4--Houston, 2013 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - 3/5--San Francisco agencies, 2013 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - 3/6--Carter Murray/DraftFCB, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - 3/6--TV Upfronts, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - 3/7--Google, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 3/7--Keep America Beautiful, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 3/8--Chobani, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - 3/8--Wunderman, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - 3/15--NBCUniversal News upfront, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - 3/18--AAAA Conference, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - 3/18--ARF/Gayle Fuguitt, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - 3/18--Honda, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - 3/19--Southwest Airlines, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - 3/20--Scripps upfront, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - 3/22--Hallmark upfront, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - 3/22--Major League Baseball, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - 3/24--TAP Project, 2013 (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - 3/25--Social media in ads, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - 3/25--Spotify, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 3/25--Temp Tee, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 3/27--Ford/JWT India, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 3/27--McCann Always On, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - 3/28--FX upfront, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - 3/29--AT, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - 3/29--Teen Vogue/Toyota, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - 4/1--76 Brand Gas/Honking, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - 4/1--April Fools, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - 4/1--Magnetik Collaborative, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - 4/2--Bravo TV, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - 4/2--Colorado, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - 4/2--NBCUniversal, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - 4/5--Mad Men (series), 2013 (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - 4/8--Builder Homesite, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 4/9--General Motors/Facebook, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - 4/9--GSN upfront, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - 4/15--Leukemia and Lymphoma Society, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - 4/15--Nike, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - 4/23--Scripps, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - 4/24--NBCUniversal, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - 4/24--Screenvision, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - 4/26--Mountain Dew, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - 4/29--Digital Content Newfronts, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - 4/29--Economist (magazine), 2013 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - 4/29--Fleishman-Hillard, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - 4/29--Gillette/BBDO, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - 4/29--Robin Hood Foundation, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - 4/30--Digital Content Newfronts, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - 5/1--Digital Content Newfronts, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - 5/2--Digital Content Newfronts, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - 5/3--Digital Content Newfronts, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - 5/6--Finlandia Cheese, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - 5/6--Newfronts, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - 5/6--Online Video/Interactive Advertisers Bureau, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - 5/6--Publishers Clearing House, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - 5/7--Mad Men IPO (series), 2013 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - 5/9--AT, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - 5/10--Oreos, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - 5/10--TV upfronts, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - 5/11--Offensive ads/Mea culpas, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - 5/13--Maaco, 2013 (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - 5/13--TV upfronts, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - 5/14--TV upfronts, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - 5/15--Hispanic television, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - 5/15--TV upfronts, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - 5/16--TV upfronts, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - 5/16--USA upfront, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - 5/17--Upfronts notes, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - 5/20--Balance Bar, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - 5/20--Upfronts wrap-up, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - 5/22--Army recruiting, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - 5/24--Skinny ads, 2013 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - 5/24--Skyword, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - 5/24--Twitter, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - 5/27--Channel 1 and 13, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - 5/28--20 Questions, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - 5/28--Grape Nuts, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - 5/30--Back to School, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - 5/31--Upfronts kickoff, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - 6/3--Danc/NYC, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - 6/3--Value/Quality, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - 6/4--Intel slogan, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - 6/6--CW upfront, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 11)
    - 6/6--Neiman/Allen Garritsen, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 12)
    - 6/7--CBS upfront, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 13)
    - 6/7--Do Something/TMI, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 14)
    - 6/10--Time Warner Cable, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 15)
    - 6/24--Bumble Bee frozen foods, 2013 (Box 162, Folder 16)
    - 6/24--Magazines with multiple covers, 2013 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - 6/24--NBC/CW upfronts, 2013 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - 6/26--Gay Games/United Church of Christ, 2013 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - 6/26--Fox upfront, 2013 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - 6/26--LGBT, 2013; 2 folders (Box 163, Folder 5-6)
    - 6/27--One Club/Real Mad Men and Women, 2013 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - 6/28--Sony upfront, 2013 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - 7/1--Planter's, 2013 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - 7/2--Building for America's Bravest, 2013 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - 7/3--Beck Bennett, 2013 (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - 7/5--Michael Houston/Grey, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - 7/8--Loew's Resorts/Catch, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - 7/8--Oscar Mayer Weinermobile, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - 7/9--Lowe Agency/Campbell Ewald, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - 7/10--Fast Company/Target, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - 7/12--Marty Weiss, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - 7/12--Smokey Bear, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - 7/15--Andy Warhol Museum, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - 7/16--Above the Influence campaign, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - 8/7--Cable TV upfront, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - 8/8--John Vassilaros, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - 8/12--Alcon/AARP, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - 8/13--Kraft recipes, 2013 (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - 8/14--BMW Diesel, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - 8/14--Publicis/Engauge, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - 8/16--Tumi, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - 8/19--Merrick Pet Care, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - 8/19--USPS/YouTube, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - 8/21--P.R.R.V., 2013 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - 8/22--TCM network, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - 8/23--Project Worldwide/Boulder, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - 8/26--University of Dayton, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - 8/26--Water Cooler Group, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - 8/27--Joan Rivers/Renuzit, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - 8/28--NFL, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - 8/30--Cross-cultural marketing, 2013 (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - 8/30--E-cigarettes, 2013; 2 folders (Box 165, Folder 14-15)
    - 9/3--Redbury Hotel, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - 9/4--Mentos, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - 9/5--GoDaddy, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - 9/9--9/11 Memorial, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - 9/9--OMD Final Front, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - 9/10--Campbell's, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - 9/11--Meineke, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - 9/12--Fall fashions, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - 9/13--IFC/Spoils of Babylon, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - 9/16--Chipotle, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - 9/16--Live Nation/Ford, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - 9/17--Berlin Cameron United/United Network, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - 9/18--Humanaut/Alex Bogusky, 2013 (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - 9/18--Lexus/Fallon, 2013 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - 9/20--Fox Super Bowl contest, 2013 (Box 167, Folder 2)